- 야, 프렌치 토스트 먹을 사람?
- 나 먹을래
-Hey. Who wants French toast?
-I'll have some.
나도, 계란과 우유는 냉장고에
고맙다
Me too. Eggs and milk in the fridge.
Thanks.
- 왜 그래?
- 손 느낌이 이상해
-What's the matter?
-My hand feels weird.
나 약혼해서 그런가봐!
I guess it's because I'm engaged!
- 신경 거슬리기 시작하면 말해
- 시작했어
-When will that start getting annoying?
-Start?
결혼식 계획
세우기 시작하자
Let's start the wedding plans.
- 그래
- 벌써?
-Okay.
-Already?
할 게 많잖아, 꽃도 생각해야지,
요리사, 음악도...
We got a lot to do. We gotta think
about the flowers, the music..
- 음악에 대한 아이디어가 있는데...
- 사공이 너무 많아
-I have thoughts on the music.
-Too many cooks...
충고할께, 신랑은 그저 나타나서
신부 이름만 제대로 말하면 돼
Take it from me. All you have to do
is show up and say the right name.
- 그건 도대체 뭐냐?
- 맙소사, 결혼식 책이야?
-What in God's name is that?
-Oh, my God, the wedding book?
4학년 이후론 처음 본다
I haven't seen that
since 4th grade.
이 책은 말야, 다 들어있어
예를 들어 장소가 필요하다
This baby has everything. Take,
you know, locations for instance:
먼저 알파벳 순으로 정리되었고
그 다음엔 지역 순으로
First organized alphabetically,
then geographically...
다음엔 평방 피트 순으로
then by square footage.
그거 너무 영리하다
That is so smart.
취소해
지금 빨리 취소해
Break it off. Break it off, now.
The One With Rachel's Book
따라서
이것이 증명하는 것은
That conclusively proves...
내가 먼저 쥬라기 공원에 대한
아이디어를 생각했다는 거죠
that I had the idea
for Jurassic Park first.
이걸 한 번 봅시다...
Let's take a look..
피비, 여기 웬일이야?
Phoebe, what are you doing here?
너랑 얘기해야 돼, 급하거든
모니카와 챈들러 일이야
I need to talk to you. It's urgent.
It's about Monica and Chandler.
어, 저런, 그래
Oh, my God. Of course.
잠깐만 실례하겠어요
Would you please excuse me
for a moment?
Do you know each other's hometowns?
Why don't you..?
서로 고향에 대해서 물어봤나?
한 번 서로 물어보지...
What's going on?
무슨 일이야?
Well, not much. I was just thinking
that since they just got engaged...
별일 없어, 그냥
둘이 금방 약혼했으니까
it would be nice
if they have privacy.
프라이버시를 좀 주면
좋지 않을까 해서
So could I just move in with you
for a couple days?
그래서, 너랑 한 이틀만
같이 묵을 수 있을까?
Okay, sure. But what's wrong
with Monica and Chandler?
물론이지, 근데 모니카랑
챈들러는 무슨 일인데?
아무 일 없어, 왜?
Nothing. Why?
급하다고 했잖아
You said it was urgent.
급했지, 영화가
5분 안에 시작하거든
Yeah, it is. My movie starts
in five minutes.
지금 교실 안에 학생들이
잔뜩 앉아있는 거 알아?
Do you realize I have a classroom
full of students?
미안, 나 너무 실례했다
누구 영화 볼 사람 있어요?
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm so rude.
Does anyone want to come to the movie?
부모님하고 예산에 대한 문제는
아직 얘기 안했지만
I haven't cleared the
budget with my parents...
음악은 이러는 게 어떨까?
but how's this for music?
결혼 행진은 현악 4중주
칵테일 시간은 재즈 트리오
A string quartet for the processional,
a jazz trio for cocktails...
댄스 음악은
베이 시티 롤러즈
the Bay City Rollers
for dancing...
잠깐, 그건 내 6학년 때 결혼식을
위한 거였잖아
Wait, that was
for my 6th grade wedding.
그 밴드는 구하지도 못할 텐데 뭐
이안은 연주를 그만뒀고, 데릭은...
You couldn't get them anyway.
Ian doesn't play anymore, and Derek...
데릭은 내가 이름을
안다는 게 웃기지
Derek is a name I shouldn't know.
모니카, 베개 또 하나 있냐?
좀 더 푹신한 걸로
Mon, do you have another pillow,
something a little snugglier?
왜 니네 집에 가서 안 자고
여기서 자냐?
Why are you napping here
instead of at your place?
- 오리 때문에
- 뭐라고, 오리?
-The duck.
-What, the duck?
그 놈의 오리가 이번엔
또 무슨 사고를 쳤어?
What the hell
did the damn duck do now?
글쎄, 저 안에서 절대
토하거나 그러진 않았어
Well, he did not get sick
somewhere in there...
그리고 당장 발견되어서
제대로 청소가 됐지
and it was immediately found
and properly cleaned up.
나도 그거 볼 순 없냐?
Do I get to look at this...
아니면 결혼식에 관련된
사람들만 보는 책인가?
or is it just for people
involved in the wedding?
당연히 볼 수 있지
네 의견도 원하거든
Of course you can look at it.
I want your opinion.
자
Here you go.
- 중앙부 꽃장식은 어때?
- 중앙부 꽃장식!
-What about centerpieces?
-Centerpieces!
- 장미, 아니면 백합?
- 당연히 장미지
-Roses or lilies?
-Definitely roses.
더 결혼식 분위기 나잖아
I think they're more "wedding-y."
- 하지만 백합이 확실한 선택이지
- 어머나, 꼭 한마음 같다
-But lilies are the clear choice.
-Oh, my God, it's like one mind.
얘들아, 얘들아
나 낮잠 자게 해줘야 돼
Guys, guys, you gotta let me nap.
안 그러면
나 짜증낸다구
I'm gonna get cranky.
조이, 복도 건너편에
아주 멀쩡한 소파가 하나 있어
Joey, there's a perfectly good couch
across the hall.
그래, 멀쩡하지...
Yes, it is perfectly good...
그리고 오리가 토한 곳 중의
하나가 절대 아니지
and it is not one of the places
the duck got sick.
뭐라고?
What?
- 알았어, 나 갈께
- 조이, 오리가 뭘 했는데?
-All right, I'm gonna go.
-Joey, what did the duck do?
몰라, 근데
네 화장 크림은 먹지 않았어
I don't know,
but he did not eat your face cream.
안녕, 녀석아, 기분 어때?
Hey, little buddy. How you feeling?
대체 그 화장 크림
안에 뭐가 들었지?
What the hell is in that face cream?
너무 부드럽다
That's so soft.
베갯잎이잖아!
Pillowcases!
'젤다는 굴뚝 청소부를 바라보았다
교구 대리인 그녀의 아버지가...'
"Zelda looked at the chimney sweep.
Her father, the vicar.."
'교구 대리'?
Vicar?
'집에 돌아오려면 아직
몇 시간이나 있었다'
"wouldn't be home for hours.
'그녀의 욕망은
불타오르고 있었다'
Her loins were burning.
'그녀는 모든 경계심을 버리고
손을 뻗어 그의...'
She threw caution to the wind
and reached out and grabbed his.."
이거 음란소설이잖아!
This is a dirty book!
피비?
Phoebe?
오, 로스, 안녕
Oh, Ross, hi.
- 피비, 뭐하는 거야?
- 미안, 지금 고객이랑 있어
-Phoebe, what are you doing?
-Sorry, I'm with a client right now.
- 피비!
- 알았어, 나가서 얘기하자
-Phoebe!
-Okay, let's talk outside.
Phoebe, you can't massage people
in my apartment.
피비, 내 아파트에서
사람들 마사지하면 안 돼
모니카와 챈들러네에서는
했는데
I did it at Monica and Chandler's.
걔네들은 알고 있었구?
And they knew about it?
알았어, 로스
진짜로 이러는 이유가 뭔데?
Okay, Ross, what is this really about?
여긴 내 집이고, 내가 원할 때
들락날락 할 수 있어야지
This is my home, and I want to be
able to come and go when I want.
나머지 예약된 고객들은
다른 데 찾아서 하지 뭐
I will find someplace else
to do the rest of my appointments.
뭐가 그리 큰 문제야?
What's the big deal?
내 아파트에 벌거벗고 기름바른
낯선 사람들이 있는게 싫어
I don't want naked,
greasy strangers in my apartment...
특히 쉬면서 퍼즐 놀이, 아니
맥주, 찬 맥주 마시고 싶을 때
when I want to kick back
with a puzzle.. Beer, cold beer.
안녕, 조이
뭐하고 있니?
Hey, Joey. What are you doing?
청소하고 있지, 왜?
널 흥분시키냐?
Sweeping. Why?
Does it turn you on?
아니
No.
내가 굴뚝을
청소하고 있었다면?
What if I was sweeping a chimney?
조이, 네가
내 화장 크림 먹었니?
Joey, did you eat my face cream?
어디 가? 교구 대리가
오려면 몇시간이나 있는데
Where are you going?
The vicar won't be home for hours.
조이, '교구 대리'
소리는 어디서 얻어들었니?
Joey, where did you learn that word?
어디서게?
Where do you think...
젤다?
Zelda?
- 너 내 책 발견했니?!
- 그래, 했지!
-You found my book?!
-Yeah, I did!
조이, 내 침실엔
왜 들어가고 난리야?
Joey, what are you doing
going into my bedroom?
미안, 그러지 말았어야 했는데
근데 너 포르노 갖고 있잖아!
I'm sorry. I know I shouldn't have,
but you got porn!
You know what? I don't care.
I'm not ashamed of my book.
있지, 난 상관 없어
창피할 것 하나도 없어
There's nothing wrong with a woman
enjoying a little erotica.
성인 여자가 성애문학을
좀 즐기는 게 큰일인가?
It's a healthy expression
of female sexuality...
그저, 건강한
여성 성욕의 표출이지
which, by the way, is something
that you will never understand.
넌 그걸 절대로
이해할 수 없겠지만 말야
You got porn.
넌 포르노 갖고 있잖아
-Hello.
-Hi, is Phoebe here?
- 안녕하세요
- 안녕, 피비 있어요?
-No, she's out for the night.
-Oh, great!
- 아니, 오늘 저녁 나갔어요
- 아이, 참!
Can I help you with something?
제가 뭐 도와드릴까요?
I don't know. Are you a masseur?
글쎄요,
댁도 안마사이신가요?
Yes, I am.
네, 그렇죠
Great! Dad?
잘됐다! 아빠?
Thank you so much.
I'll pick him up in an hour.
너무 고마워요
한 시간 안에 모시러 올께요
Your parents must've been thrilled
when you told them you were engaged.
자네 부모는 약혼했다는
소식 듣고 아주 신나하셨겠다
Oh, yeah.
I should probably call them.
오, 그래요
언제 전화드려야 할 텐데
I remember when we first got engaged.
우리 약혼했을 때가
생각나는구나
-I've never heard that story.
-Dad..
- 그 얘긴 한 번도 못들었는데요
- 아빠, 얘기 하지...
Well, I'd gotten Judy pregnant.
그러니까, 그 때
내가 주디를 임신시켰지
I still don't know how.
아직도 그게 어떻게
된 일인지 모르겠어
You don't know how? Your dog
thought my diaphragm was a chew toy.
몰라요? 당신 개가 내 피임 기구를
장난감인 줄 알고 물어뜯었잖아요
What a sweet story.
참 아름다운 얘기군요
You're not hearing it
at your 5th grade Halloween party.
난 5학년 할로윈 파티 때
처음 이 얘길 들었는걸
They wanted a scary story.
그 때 무서운 얘기
해달라고 해서
We're excited
about our wedding plans.
결혼식 계획하는 게
무척 기대돼요
Pretty soon we'll be making a big
withdrawal from the wedding fund.
결혼식 기금도 곧
큰 지출을 보게 생겼는데요
-What?
-You tell her, Jack. I can't do it.
- 왜요?
- 당신이 말해요, 난 못하겠어
You have the wedding fund, don't you?
결혼식 기금은
아직 갖고 계시죠?
We have it.
Only now we call it "the beach house."
갖고 있지, 근데 이젠
'해변 별장'이라고 부르지
제 결혼식 기금을
해변 별장에다 썼다구요?
You spent my wedding
fund on the beach house?
미안하다, 우린 단지
We're sorry. We assumed...
30이 되면 네 스스로
결혼식 비용을 낼 줄 알았지
that when you turned 30
you'd pay for it yourself.
해변 별장은
제가 23살 때 샀잖아요
You bought the beach house
when I was 23.
So you've had seven years
of beach fun...
그래서 7년간 해변에서
즐거운 시간 보냈잖니?
그건 값을 매길 수
없는 거라구
and you can't put a price on that.
We do feel bad about this.
우린 무척
유감스러워하고 있어
We saved again
when you dated Richard.
네가 리처드를 사귈 때
또 저축했는데
Then that went to hell,
so we redid the kitchen.
근데, 그것도 파탄나서
그 돈을 부엌 고치는 데 썼지
제가 챈들러
사귀기 시작할 때는요?
What about Chandler?
챈들러잖아, 얘가
청혼할 거라곤 생각 안했지
It was Chandler.
We didn't think he'd propose.
제가 아무래도 아까 술을
덜 마셨었던 것 같군요
I didn't start drinking
enough at the start of the meal.
결혼식에 쓸 돈이 없다니
믿을 수 없어요
I can't believe there's no money.
네 아빠가 만일에
인터넷으로 얼음을
Maybe, if your father hadn't tried...
팔려고만 안했더라면
돈이 좀 있었을 지 몰라
to sell ice over the lnternet.
- 참 간단한 아이디어였는데
- '바보 같은' 아이디어였어요
-It seemed like such a simple idea.
-Stupid. The word is "stupid."
그만해, 이제
더 이상 듣고 싶지 않아
Enough. I don't want
to hear about it anymore.
행운을 비네, 챈들러
Good luck, Chandler.
자, 이제 제가...
Okay, now I'm going to...
만지겠습니다
touch you.
오, 두부 같다
That's soft.
너네 부모님이 도와 주실순
없을까?
Do you think your parents
could help pay for it?
글쎄다
I don't know.
My mother spent most of her money
on her fourth wedding.
우리 엄마는 돈 대부분을
당신 4번째 결혼식에다 썼지
나머지는 이혼을
대비해 절약해두고 있구
Saving the rest for her divorce.
아버지는 돈이 남아돌면
매년 여행하는데 쓰시지
And any extra cash my father has,
he saves for his yearly trips to...
가수 돌리 파튼 유원지 관광
Dollywood.
- 저녁 식사 때 무슨 일 있었어?
- 부모님이 내 결혼식 기금을 써버렸어
-What happened at dinner?
-My parents spent the wedding fund.
어머나, 뭘 시켰는데?
My God, what did you order?
잠깐만, 돈이 없다구?
이거 너무 나쁜데
Wait, there's no money?
Well, this is terrible.
그럼, 너희들 노인정
같은 데서 결혼해야 되잖아
You guys will have to get
married in, like, a rec center.
-Honey, it's gonna be okay.
-No, it's not gonna be okay.
- 자기야, 괜찮을 거야
- 아니야, 괜찮지 않아
-No swing band, no lilies.
-It's gonna be okay.
- 스윙 밴드도 없고, 백합도 없고
- 아냐, 괜찮을 거야
I mean, you don't need to have this...
이런 것 필요 없잖아
전원적 이태리식
요리 같은 것
rustic ltalian feast.
You don't need this custom-made...
이런 맞춤복도 필요없고...
empire waist, duchess satin gown.
엠파이어 웨이스트 라인의
공단 드레스 따위 말야
그냥 기성복 사 입지 뭐
You can wear off-the-rack.
It's really gonna be okay.
정말 괜찮다니까
The important thing is, we love each
other and we're gonna get married.
중요한 건, 우리가 서로 사랑하고
결혼할 거라는 사실이지
Do you even understand what
"off-the-rack" means?
'기성복'의 뜻이
뭔지 이해하기나 해?
Why don't you pay for it yourself?
그냥 너희들이 돈을 쓰지 그래?
I don't have any money.
어떻게?
난 돈이 하나도 없어
-I have some.
-How much?
- 난 조금 있어
- 얼마나?
Well, close to...
글쎄, 한...
-Are you kidding me?!
-How much?
- 이거 진담이야?!
- 얼만데?
-Enough for wedding scenario A.
-Really?
- 웨딩 시나리오 A가 가능할 만큼이야
- 정말?
너 정말 대단하구나
요 야무진 절약가야!
How great are you, you little saver!
그 돈이 바로 내 꿈의
결혼식 예산과 맞아떨어져
This is exactly
the budget of my dream wedding.
너희 둘이 천생연분이다
You guys are so made for each other.
결혼식에다 돈을 다 쓰자고
제안하는 건 설마 아니겠지?
You're not suggesting we spend
all the money on the wedding?
물론이지
Yeah.
이봐, 모니카
난 이 돈을 6년간 모았어
Look, Mon, I've been saving this money
for six years...
그 일부는 미래를 위해서 쓰고 싶어
한 파티에다 날리고 싶진 않아
and I have some of it earmarked
for the future, not just for a party.
와! 안녕, 미스터 챈들러
Wow! Hello, Mr. Chandler.
자기, 이 날은 우리 일생의
가장 특별한 날이잖아
Sweetie, this is the most special day
of our lives.
그건 아는데, 자기야, 난
한 파티에다 돈을 다 쓰진 않을 거야
I realize that, honey, but I won't
spend all the money on one party.
자기야, 자기 사랑해
Honey, I love you.
근데, 우리 결혼식을
또 한 번만 파티라고 부르면
But if you call our wedding
a party one more time...
자기는 초대가 안될 지도 몰라
you may not get invited.
우린 언제나 돈은 더 벌 수 있어
결혼은 딱 한 번만 하잖아
We can always earn more money.
We're only gonna get married once.
이해하는데 난 이번엔 단호한
입장을 취해야겠어, 대답은 '노'야
I understand, but I have to put
my foot down. The answer is no.
단호한 입장을 취한다고?
You're gonna have
to put your foot down?
그래
Yes, I am.
돈도 있고, 통제력도 있고
Money and a firm hand.
드디어 상당히 맘에 드는
챈들러 모습을 보는구먼
Finally a Chandler
I can get onboard with.
'센트럴
퍼크'
- 안녕, 레이첼
- 조이
-Hey, Rach.
-Joey.
야, 레이첼
연기 냄새 안나냐?
Hey, Rach, do you smell smoke?
그래, 알았어, 연기, 굴뚝
굴뚝 청소부, 웃긴다, 하하
I get it. Smoke, chimney,
chimney sweep. Very funny. Ha, ha.
아니, 아니, 진짜로
냄새 안나?
No, no, I'm serious.
You don't smell it?
뭔가 불타고 있는데
Something's on fire.
아무 냄새 안나는데
I don't smell anything.
있잖아, 아마 그냥
너의 불타오르는 욕망일 거야
You know what? It's probably
just your burning loins.
- 야, 무슨 얘기들 하냐?
- 아무것도 아냐
-Hey, what are you guys talking about?
-Nothing.
야, 이 커피가 찬데
Damn, this coffee's cold.
이걸 너의 불타오르는
욕망에다 데울 순 없을까?
Do you mind if I heat this
on your loins?
너, 정말, 조이
그런 얘길 왜 했어?
You know, I cannot believe
you told him. Joey...
우리가 헤어진 다음에
그 책을 샀나보지?
I guess you bought that book
after we broke up.
그렇지, 처음에 샀던 책은
너랑 사귈 동안 다 닳아빠졌지
I did, because I wore out my first
copy when I was with you.
오, 그래?
Oh, yeah?
우리가 사귈 땐
난 포르노 잡지를 잔뜩 읽었다!
Well, when we were going out,
I read tons of porno magazines.
어이
Sup?
로스, 어떻게 나이 많은
할아버지한테 그럴 수 있어?
Ross, how could you do that
to an old man?
실례해요, 아가씨들
Excuse me, ladies.
뭐라고?
I'm sorry?
내 안마 고객, 아더 말이야
My massage client. Arthur.
그의 딸이 그러잖아
날 위해 일하는 어떤 남자가
His daughter said some guy
that worked for me...
굉장히 이상한
마사지를 해줬다고
gave him a really weird massage.
난 아주 전문적인
마사지를 했어
I gave him an extremely
professional massage.
네가 나무 숟가락으로
마구 찔렀다고 하던데
He said you poked
at him with wooden spoons.
알았어, 기존의
마사지하곤 좀 달랐어
Okay, so it wasn't
a traditional massage.
하지만, 젓가락 갖고
지압도 해줬고
But I did give him acupressure
with a pair of chopsticks...
또, 피부 때도 살짝 밀어줬지
...자루걸레 갖고
and I gently exfoliated him
with a mop.
어쨌든 다시는 나한테 안온대
너 땜에 일주일에 80달러 잃었어
Well, he's never coming back.
You just cost me $80 a week.
이건 네 탓이야
네가 약속을 안 옮겼잖아
This is your fault.
You didn't move his appointment.
오, 내 탓이라고?
네가 그 사람 안마할 필요가 있었어?
Oh, it's my fault?
You didn't have to massage him.
그냥 보냈으면 됐을 거 아냐
You could've sent him away.
그 사람 등에다 장난감 트럭을
굴릴 필요는 없었잖아
You could've not rolled Tonka trucks
up and down his back.
그건 그 사람이
기분 좋다고 했는데 뭐!
He said he liked that!
맞아, 네가 맞아
미안해
You're right, you're right.
I'm sorry.
야, 나이든 할아버지
마사지는 왜 하고 있냐?
Dude, what are you massaging
an old man for?
- 딸이 끝내줬거든
- 알겠다
-His daughter was hot.
-Gotcha.
저기...
Listen...
나 생각해봤는데...
I've been thinking.
내가 너더러 우리 결혼식에다
돈을 다 쓰라는 건 불공평했어
It's not fair of me to ask you to
spend all your money on our wedding.
넌 그 돈을 벌기 위해
아주 열심히 일하잖아
I mean, you work really hard for that.
- 글쎄
- 어쨌든 일하잖아
-Well.
-Well, you work for that.
이봐, 나도 생각해봤어
Look, I've thought about it too.
미안해, 그 돈 모두를
결혼식에다 쓰는 게 좋겠어
I'm sorry. I think we should spend
all the money on the wedding.
- 정말로?
- 그래, 단호한 입장을 취하겠어
-You do?
-Yeah, I'm putting my foot down.
내가 너한테
청혼 했을 때
Look, when I proposed,
I told you...
너의 행복을 위해서라면
무슨 일이든 하겠다고 했지
that I would do anything
to make you happy.
완벽한 결혼식을 갖는 게
널 행복하게 한다면
And if having the perfect wedding
makes you happy...
그렇게 할 거야
then that's what we're gonna do.
자기 너무 사랑스러워
You are so sweet.
근데, 미래랑은 어떻고?
What about the future and stuff?
미래랑은 잊어버려
Forget about the future and stuff.
애를 둘만 갖지 뭐
So we only have two kids.
그 중 제일 좋아하는 애 하나만
골라서 대학에 보내지 뭐
We'll pick our favorite and
that one will get to go to college.
- 그런 것도 생각해봤어?
- 그럼
-Have you thought about that?
-Yeah.
How many kids were we gonna have?
원래는 애를
몇 명 가지려 했는데?
네 명, 아들 하나
쌍둥이 딸, 또 아들 하나
Four. A boy, twin girls
and another boy.
또 어떤 걸 생각해봤는데?
What else did you think about?
글쎄, 우리가 어디서 살 건지
뭐 그런 거
Well, stuff like where we'd live,
you know.
도시 외곽에
작은 집을 얻으면 어떨까?
Like a small place outside the city...
우리 애들이 자전거
배울 수 있는 곳이면 좋겠지?
where our kids could learn
to ride their bikes.
또, 고양이를 얻어서
목에 방울을 달면
We could have a cat that had a bell
on its collar...
문을 들락거릴 때마다
방울 소리가 들리겠지
and we could hear it every time
it ran through the little kitty door.
차고 위에는 방 하나 있어서
조이가 여생을 보내게 하면 될거야
We'd have an apartment over the garage
where Joey could grow old.
있잖아
You know what?
나 크고 화려한
결혼식 원치 않아
I don't want a big, fancy wedding.
- 무슨 소리야?
- 아냐
-Sure you do.
-No.
난 네가 지금 말한 모든 걸 원해
난 결혼생활을 원해
I want everything that you've
just said. I want a marriage.
확실해?
You sure?
- 자기 너무 사랑해
- 사랑해
-I love you so much.
-I love you.
미래에 대한 얘기했을 때 말야
고양이 얘기를 했는데
When you were talking
about our future, you said cat.
개 얘기를 하는 거였지, 그치?
But you meant dog, right?
- 그럼, 물론이지
- 좋았어
-Totally.
-Good.
안녕, 젤다
Hello, Zelda.
- 너 누구 흉내내는 거냐?
- 교구 대리
-Who are you supposed to be?
-The vicar.
- 교구 대리가 뭔지 알기나 해?
- 골키퍼 같은 거지, 안그래?
-Do you even know what a vicar is?
-Like a goalie, right?
조이, 정말이야, 응?
Look, that's enough.
바보 같은 농담에
저질스럽게 빈정거리는 거
You make stupid jokes
and sleazy innuendoes...
이제 더 이상 웃기지 않아
-and it's just not funny anymore.
-I'm sorry. Rach, I'm sorry.
미안해, 레이첼, 미안
내가 대신에... 외양간에서
거칠게 다뤄주는 게 어떨까?
Maybe I could make it up to you
by taking you roughly in the barn.
알았어, 됐어, 이제
너 하고 싶어? 하자구
All right, that's it.
You want to do it? Let's do it.
그래
너랑 하고 싶어
That's right.
I want to do it with you.
여태껏 억제해왔는데
네가 적절한 말로 날 유혹했다
Been trying to fight it,
but you said all the right things.
내가 그랬어?
I did?
그래, 너무나 오랫동안
너의 몸을 기다려왔어
Yeah, I been waiting for so long
to get on that body.
- 이 몸을?
- 그래, 맞아
-This body?
-Yeah, that's right.
얼른, 조이, 덤벼봐
Come on, Joey, sex me up.
너 7장에 있는 정육점 주인
아내같이 들리기 시작한다
You're starting to sound like
the butcher's wife in chapter seven.
어서, 지금
나 기다리게 하지마, 옷을 벗어
Come on, now. Don't keep me
waiting. Take your clothes off.
근데, 그 헬멧은 그대로 쓰고
있는게 좋겠다, 좀 거칠 테니까
But I'd keep that helmet on,
because you're in for a rough ride.
안할래, 무서워
I don't want to. I'm scared.